codingdojo.com 2018-11-24

# COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

                                                CODING DOJO
                                              PRIVACY POLICY
Updated: 12/10/15 Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy explains how Coding Dojo, LLC (“Coding Dojo,” “we” or “us”) collects, uses and
discloses information when you access or use our websites and other online products and services
(collectively, the “Coding Dojo Service Offerings”) or when you otherwise interact with us.
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by
revising the date at the top of the policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional
notice (such as adding a statement to the homepages of our websites or sending you an email
notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Coding Dojo
Service Offerings to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect
your privacy.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US
We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you:
create an account; join our partner program; make a payment; use any Coding Dojo Service Offering;
contact customer service; respond to questionnaires; or otherwise interact with us. The types of
information we may collect vary depending on the Coding Dojo Service Offerings you use and
may include your name, email address, phone number, postal address and contact details for your
organization if applicable.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY WHEN YOU USE THE CODING DOJO SERVICE
OFFERINGS
When you access or use the Coding Dojo Service Offerings, we may automatically collect information
about you, including:
      • Log Information: We log information about your use of the Coding Dojo Service
		          Offerings, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed,
		          your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to the Coding Dojo
		          Service Offerings.
      • Device Information: We collect information about the computer or mobile device
		          you use to access the Coding Dojo Service Offerings, including, but not limited to,
		          configuration information, network speed, hardware model, operating system and
		          version and information about the software on your computer or device.
                                                                                                Page 1 of 4

                                            CODING DOJO
                                           PRIVACY POLICY
     •   Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We use various
		       technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your
		       computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or
		       in device memory that helps us to improve the Coding Dojo Service Offerings and
		       your experience, see which areas and features of the Coding Dojo Service Offerings
		       are popular and count visits. We may also collect information using web beacons (also
		       known as “tracking pixels”). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in
		       the Coding Dojo Service Offerings or our emails and help deliver cookies, count visits,
		       understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has
		       been opened and acted upon. For more information about cookies, and how to disable
		       them, please see “Your Choices” below.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM OTHER SOURCES
We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect
through the Coding Dojo Service Offerings.
USE OF INFORMATION
We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:
     • Provide, maintain and improve the Coding Dojo Service Offerings, process transactions
		       and send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices,
		       updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
     • Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
     • Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and
		       events offered by Coding Dojo and others, and provide news and information we
		       think will be of interest to you;
     • Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
     • Personalize and improve the Coding Dojo Service Offerings and provide advertisements,
		       content or features that match user profiles or interests;
     • Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs
		       and provide you with better service; and
     • Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.
Coding Dojo is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law.
By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the
processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.
SECURITY
Coding Dojo takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft,
misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
                                                                                              Page 2 of 4

                                                 CODING DOJO
                                               PRIVACY POLICY
SHARING OF INFORMATION
We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:
      • With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such
		         information to carry out work on our behalf;
      • If you live in a jurisdiction where we have an arrangement with a third party reseller
		         or consultant, or if you are using a partner-branded version of the Coding Dojo Service
		         Offerings, we will share information about you with the reseller, consultant or partner to
		         provide you with the products and services you requested;
      • If you establish an account with Coding Dojo after clicking an affiliate link on a third party
		         website, or if your account registration identifies a Coding Dojo partner who referred you
		         to Coding Dojo, your domain name and the time of your referral will be displayed to that
		         partner for tracking purposes, but Coding Dojo will not share the remainder of your email
		         address or any other identifying information (e.g., If JohnDoe@domainsample.com is
		         referred by a Coding Dojo partner at 12 noon on January 1, 2010, the partner could
		         access an administrative page indicating that Coding Dojo received a referral of someone
		         from domainsample.com at that time);
      • If you participate in any interactive areas of the Coding Dojo Service Offerings (such as a
		         bulletin board, blog or chat room), the information you provide may be displayed publicly;
      • In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any
		         applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law,
		         rule or regulation;
      • If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements
		         or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Coding Dojo or others;
      • In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing
		         or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and
      • With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through the Coding Dojo
		         Service Offerings that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner
		         and you provide such information.
We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to
identify you.
ANALYTICS SERVICES PROVIDED BY OTHERS
We may engage third parties to provide analytics services in connection with the Coding Dojo
Service Offerings. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect
and analyze information about your use of the Services, including but not limited to your IP address,
browser type, access times, and pages visited. We use this information to measure activity, generate
statistics and improve the usefulness of the Coding Dojo Service Offerings.
                                                                                                 Page 3 of 4

                                               CODING DOJO
                                              PRIVACY POLICY
YOUR CHOICES
ACCOUNT INFORMATION
You may update or correct information about you at any time by logging into your online account.
COOKIES
Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set
your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject
cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Coding Dojo Service Offerings.
PROMOTIONAL COMMUNICATIONS
You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from Coding Dojo by following the
instructions in those communications or logging in to your account and updating your contact
preferences. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as
messages about your account or our ongoing business relations.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: info@codingdojo.com.
                                                                                                 Page 4 of 4
